

## **Nicholas Moschouris**

631-220-8384

nmosch@gmail.com

**Profile** 

**Github** 

JavaScript - CSS - HTML

## **Profile**

Full stack web developer utilizing financial advising background to analyze complex problems and build creative solutions. Certificate in full stack development from University of Arizona with an emphasis in JavaScript, Node.js, React, CSS, and HTML. Customer first experience helped me to understand what front end users want and deliver those features. Focusing on a mobile-first design and intuitive features, easy to navigate UI, and RESTful APIs, I'm excited to use my creativity and critical thinking to help your team realize their goals and create engaging, exciting web experiences. Please see my Github and portfolio page to review some of my work.

### **Technical Skills**

JavaScript HTML CSS Node.JS JQuery React MongoDB MySQL Git TDD PWA

#### Education

W.P. Carey School of Business, Arizona State University, Tempe, AZ; 2004-2007 – Bachelors of Business Management

University of Arizona Full Stack Web Development Program, Gilbert AZ, Feb 2020 – Aug 2020

# Experience

**CUSTOMER DEVELOPMENT, GODADDY: GILBERT, AZ – 3/2020-PRESENT** 

Technical support for website hosting, SSLs, website security, emails and domains settings to ensure customer's business websites were running securely and efficiently

Identified opportunities to improve customer web presence by recommending appropriate products and setting products up to ensure compatibility

FINANCIAL ADVISOR, VANGUARD: SCOTTSDALE, AZ - 10/2012-8/2019

Developed financial plans for customers based on unique variables including expected retirement income, savings rates, annualized return projections, and life expectancy.

Adhered to regulatory and firm level compliance through QA of written plans and thorough documentation of client qualifications.

CREDIT/MARGIN OPERATIONS, VANGUARD: SCOTTSDALE, AZ - 11/2010-9/2012

Completed 3-5 tasks daily including department reporting, task delegation, processing assigned functions, QA of other's work, and providing support to front-line client reps.

Analyzed trading patterns for 20-30 clients daily to determine if trading violations occurred. Once identified, appropriate restrictions were applied to the account and clients contacted for detailed explanations.

Partnered with 4-6 departments daily to verify complex issues were resolved in a manner consistent with company standards, industry requirements, and client expectations.

References - Available upon request